britbox.com 2017-10-02

# BritBox - Privacy Policy

* * *

BritBox is a service run by BritBox, LLC.

BritBox respects your right to privacy. We’re committed to being transparent about our use of your information and the choices available to you. This policy tells you what information we may collect, how we collect it and what we might do with it. By accessing and using our services you agree to our use of your information as described in this policy. If you have any questions, please don’t hesitate to contact us at[privacy-us@britbox.com](mailto:privacy-us@britbox.com).

* * *

 **Updates to this policy** : This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time to reflect changes in law or best practice, or changes in our business practices. Material changes will be clearly highlighted and we’ll take reasonable steps to notify you of any changes that impact on your privacy. The date of the most recent revision will appear at the top of this page. You should check this policy each time you provide information to us.

  1. What information we might collect about you
  2. How we use this information
  3. When we may share your information with others
  4. Where we will store and use your information
  5. How long we’ll keep your information
  6. Your Choices
  7. Children
  8. Cookies and tracking technologies used through our website, apps and emails
  9. My California Law Rights
  10. Governing Law
  11. Contact us
  12. Glossary: What are cookies and tracking technologies?

* * *

## 1\. WHAT INFORMATION WE MIGHT COLLECT ABOUT YOU

 **Data you give us** : We collect information from you when you register to use our services, sign up to receive marketing emails from us or when you contact customer services. This may consist of your name, email address, billing address, payment card details and any other information you volunteer to us (for example, when you contact customer services). We’ll only use this supplementary information to deal with your query or for the purposes explained to you at the time the information was collected.

When you subscribe to BritBox, to enable us to process your payments and provide access to you, you’re required to submit: your name, email address, billing address, and payment card details.

 **Data we collect automatically** : When you use the BritBox service, we’ll collect technical information about your use and browsing of our website and apps and about the device you’re using to access the services. For example, we receive your IP address when your device talks to our servers so we can send content to the right device.

We sometimes also collect information about the model and version of the device, browser and operating system you’re using; data about how you use the service and what you view; your device’s network and connections; your network and/or GPS location. We also collect unique IDs from your device – like randomly generated cookie IDs or your mobile device’s Ad ID (a value assigned by the operating system, which you can reset or limit). To collect this information, we use cookies and other tracking technologies. You can find more information about these technologies inSection 8of this policy.

 **Data we collect from social media services and other third parties** : We may obtain information about you from other services, such as your publicly available profile or posts or, if you use a social media account to register or sign-in to our service, your social media provider will ask your permission to share account information with us to enable sign in. Any information we collect through these services will be treated in accordance with this policy.

 **Information we buy-in from data specialists** : We may purchase data from specialist data resellers, including demographic information, publicly available information, purchase data and advertiser data.

* * *

## 2\. HOW WE USE THIS INFORMATION

We aim to use your information in ways that are fair and reasonable. Generally speaking, we and our service providers might use your information to:

  * Provide services and functionality you request from us; for example to create an account for you and to enable you to subscribe to our services
  * Personalise our services and our marketing; this will usually be based on your browsing and viewing behaviour, as well as any demographic information we hold about you
  * Send marketing to you, including content recommendations and special offers in accordance with your marketing preferences/choices
  * Provide technical support and send service messages; for example, to let you know if a new version of our app is available, or if there will be any maintenance carried out on the service
  * Invite you to participate in surveys, user testing and panels
  * Administer prize draws and competitions which you choose to enter – including publishing the names of winners, if required
  * Analyse your use of our services to help us to understand how the services are used and to improve them for everyone
  * Enforce our rights and terms of service
  * Prevent fraud or other potentially illegal activities (including copyright infringement)
  * Manage our email suppression lists.

 **Aggregate and/or Anonymised Information** : We may aggregate or anonymise certain information that we collect from you. Aggregate and de-identified information is designed so that we can’t identify you personally.

* * *

We won’t sell or rent your data to others. We may share your information outside BritBox in the following circumstances:

 **Our service providers** : We use a number of third parties to perform business functions on our behalf, such as sending our newsletters, hosting our online services and providing our customer services. We only disclose the information necessary to enable these third parties to perform their services. Our suppliers are contracted to comply with our instructions and we require that they don’t use your personal information for their own business purposes. For our Canadian users, our Data Protection Officer (whose contact information is provided inSection 11of this Policy), can provide further information about our policies and practices regarding service providers located outside of Canada and further information about how these service providers collect, use, disclose and store personal information on our behalf.

 **Payment partners** : We use specialist payment partners to process your payment card information. In processing your payments, they may also use the data for fraud detection and prevention. They’re obliged to remain certified as compliant with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) security standards.

 **Social media networks and other third parties** : Generally we’ll only share your data with other third parties if you consent to this or ask us to share it.

We may also share information with these networks so we can market to you through their services and to help us to market to people with similar interests to you. For example, some services allow us to upload our customer list to match them to their users in a secure form – using a technology called hashing, which makes the data unreadable unless the other company has the same data. We require that all non-matches are securely deleted from their systems.

 **Regulatory bodies and others** : We may disclose your personal information to law enforcement agencies, government/regulatory bodies, internet service providers and content protection organisations as required or allowed by law. For example, if you post inappropriate or objectionable content on our services or where we reasonably believe you may be in breach of the law, we may report your content and behaviour to relevant parties.

 **Sale or transfer of all or part of our business or assets** : We reserve the right to transfer your personal information if we sell or transfer all or a part of our business or assets so the buyer can continue to offer you the services. In such circumstances, we’ll make reasonable efforts to give you advance notification of the transfer of your information.

* * *

## 4\. WHERE WE’LL STORE AND USE YOUR INFORMATION

Your information will be processed in the United States and other locations globally, where it may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement.

As described in the previous section, we may share your information with related companies or with third party service providers and social networks. These companies may be located in, or use IT equipment located in, countries different to that in which your information is collected. Where this is the case, we’ll take steps to ensure your information receives an equivalent level of protection.

* * *

## 5\. HOW LONG WE’LL KEEP YOUR INFORMATION

We’ll keep your information for as long as you use our services and for a period of time after you have stopped using the services for analysis and administrative purposes. We may keep an anonymised form of your account for a longer period, but it won’t be possible to link this data back to you.

Our payment partners will keep certain payment information for as long as required by law.

* * *

## 6\. YOUR CHOICES

 **Email Marketing & Direct Mail**: You can opt-out from email marketing at any time bychanging your preference in your account settingsor by clicking on the unsubscribe link in each marketing email we send to you. You can also opt-out from email marketing and direct mail by contacting us at[privacy-us@britbox.com](mailto:privacy-us@britbox.com).

In accordance with industry standards, we reserve the right to retain your record for suppression purposes for a reasonable amount of time so we can ensure we don’t contact you in the future.

 **Cookies & Tracking Technologies**: You can find information about your options to limit or opt-out inSection 8.

 **Deleting your account** : If you’d like us to delete information about you from our records, please contact us via customer services or by using the details below. Please note that we may be required to retain certain information by law and/or for legitimate business purposes.

 **Accessing and correcting your information** : Much of the information we hold about you is accessible and/or amendable via your account. If you’d like a copy of other information we may hold about you, you can submit a request to us by using the contact details below. Please supply as much information as possible to help us to locate your information. We reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for this service and to protect your privacy we’ll require proof of identity before granting access to your personal information.

We’ll always endeavour to supply, correct or delete personal information about you on our files within a reasonable time, or as required by law.

* * *

## 7\. CHILDREN

BritBox does not direct its services to children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not knowingly collect information from such children. We require all users of the services to be at least thirteen (13) years old. If we obtain actual knowledge that a user is under the age of thirteen (13), we will promptly delete all information associated with such account. By using the services, you are representing that you are at least thirteen (13) years old.

* * *

## 8\. COOKIES & TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES USED THROUGH OUR WEBSITE, APPS AND EMAILS

Like most companies, we (and our service providers) use specialist web and app technologies, including cookies. You can find out about these specific types of technologies inSection 12.

We use these technologies for a variety of purposes, including those outlined below.

 **Operating our services** : for example, to keep you signed in, to secure our services and your information, plus other system administration purposes.

 **Providing features and functionality to improve your experience** : such as enabling you to save your preferences and playback settings or to remember your playback progress.

 **Analysing use of our services to optimise and improve our services** : we monitor and measure how our services are used, as well as the effectiveness of our email and online marketing campaigns, so we can optimise and improve how we operate.

We use third party analytics services on our website and apps to help us analyse how users interact with and use our services, compile reports regarding activity on our services, and provide other services. These analytics services use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect information about your use of our services, plus technical data such as your IP address, browser type and version, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, or any referring website. The information generated by these analytics services will be transmitted to and stored by them and will be subject to their privacy policies.

Examples of the services we may use for analytics include:

  *  **Google Analytics** :

    * Opt-out:[tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)
    * Privacy Policy:[www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)
  *  **Google Advertising (for demographics & interest analytics)**:

    * Opt-out:[www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)
    * Privacy policy:[www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

 **Personalising and marketing of our services (online adverting)** : We use cookies and other technologies to personalise content based on your viewing and browsing behaviour.

We may also use advertising companies to serve our online marketing to you elsewhere on the web. These companies may use tracking technologies to collect information about your use of our services, which they use to target our marketing messages to you. They may also collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites, as well as other online services so they can better understand your interests, and serve you with relevant adverts. Some of these services may hold personally identifiable information and they may match this to your browsing behaviour for their own profiling and advertising purposes.

Examples of the services we use for personalisation and marketing include:

  *  **Google Advertising** :

    * Opt-out:[www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)
    * Privacy Policy:[www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)
  *  **Facebook Advertising** :

    * Opt-out: If you have a Facebook account:[www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads), If you don’t:[www.aboutads.info/choices/](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/)
    * Privacy Policy:[www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

 **Sharing tools and social media** : We may provide you with the ability to share pages or information via third parties, for services such as social sharing. When you interact with these services they may collect information from and about you, as well as your interaction with their content. This activity will be subject to the privacy policy of and your settings for your chosen network. It’s important to be aware that they may track your activity, through the use of cookies or similar technology, without you needing to interact with them. If this concerns you, make sure you log out of their services before using ours.

 **Your Choices** : You can limit some of the tracking technologies that collect information when you use our services by using the opt-out tools provided by our service providers (see above) and ad industry bodies or by changing your device settings as described below.

 _Advertising Industry Opt-Out Tools_ : Advertising companies that serve interest-based advertising may participate in self-regulatory programs such as the Digital Advertising Alliance and the Network Advertising Initiative. Both programs provide tools that enable you to opt out from your browsing data being used by these companies to customize adverts to your interests:

  * Digital Advertising Alliance:[www.aboutads.info/choices/](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/)
  * Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada:[youradchoices.ca/choices/](https://youradchoices.ca/choices/)
  * Network Advertising Initiative:[www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

 _Browser settings_ : Many web browsers automatically accept cookies (and LSO’s and HTML5 storage), but you can usually modify your browser’s setting to decline cookies if you prefer or delete them when you close your browser; you’ll find instructions for this on your browser’s help menu. If you choose to decline cookies, certain features of our services may not function properly or become inaccessible to you. In addition, you may also render some technologies unusable by rejecting or removing their associated cookies. Note that if you choose to remove cookies, you may remove opt-out cookies that affect your online marketing preferences.

 _Mobile device settings_ : Similarly, you can learn how to opt out of mobile app tracking by certain advertising networks through the privacy and/or advertising settings on your device. To find out how to change these settings for Apple, Android or Windows devices, see:

  * Apple:[support.apple.com/en-gb/HT202074](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT202074)
  * Android:[www.google.co.uk/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.co.uk/policies/technologies/ads/)
  * Windows:[choice.microsoft.com/en-in/opt-out](https://choice.microsoft.com/en-in/opt-out)

 _Email settings_ : We measure the effectiveness of our email marketing campaigns through the use of a pixel, or image file. You can opt out by turning off images in your email client – your provider may set them to ‘off’ by default.

 _‘Do Not Track’ (DNT) signals sent by your browser_ : Your browser or device may include ‘Do Not Track’ functionality. As there’s no common industry standard, we don’t currently respond to ‘Do Not Track’ signals. We continue to monitor industry and technological developments in this area and may adopt a standard if one is agreed. In the meantime, you can control the cookies as described above.

* * *

## 9\. MY CALIFORNIA LAW RIGHTS

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their “personal information” (as defined under the California Online Privacy Protection Act), if any, for that third party’s direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of “personal information” disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request in an email to[privacy-us@britbox.com](mailto:privacy-us@britbox.com).

* * *

## 10\. GOVERNING LAW

This Privacy Policy and all disputes arising hereunder or relating hereto shall be governed by, and will be construed under, the laws of the State of New York, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law principles. BritBox may limit the website’s availability, in whole or in part, concerning any person, geographic area or jurisdiction, at any time in its sole discretion.

* * *

  * Data Protection Officer
  * BritBox LLLC
  * 1120 Avenue of the Americas, FL 5
  * New York, New York 10036

* * *

## 12\. GLOSSARY: What are cookies and tracking technologies?

Websites and Apps you use, including this service, may use a combination of the following technologies:

 _Cookies, LSOs and HTML5 storage_ : These are distinct yet similar technologies which use small text files to store a randomly assigned ID and a website reference ID on your device to enable a website to ‘recognise’ it. They’re not usually used to store personal information. Some cookies will be deleted when you leave the website (session cookies) and others will persist so your device can be recognised and tracked over time – for example, for analytical purposes, to keep you signed in, or to remember media playback data. They may be set by the website you visit or by other companies providing services to/via that website (‘third party cookies’). Cookies can be controlled via your browser settings, and by using the opt-out tools. Be aware that opt-out tools work by setting an opt-out cookie, which tells the website not to track you. So if you then delete/clear your cookies you’ll delete the opt-out.

 _Tags, pixels and web beacons_ : These are all terms for pieces of code invisibly embedded in the webpage which transmit a reference code to enable websites and companies to track traffic and your interaction with a website, app or email. They’re often used in conjunction with cookies to see how you navigate the website. You can render them ineffective by opting out from the related cookies.

 _HTTP referrers_ : When you navigate to a website, the page you originated from or the URL you clicked on will be sent to the website. This is then logged and used to help understand more about your user journey, or to analyse the effectiveness of marketing campaigns.

 _Device fingerprinting_ : Websites using this technology will collect a wide range of technical data about your device, browser and operating system which enables them to uniquely identify your device with high precision without relying on other technologies. This can therefore be used if you’ve set your browser to refuse cookies.

 _Software Development Kits (SDKs)_ : These are small programs contained within mobile apps to provide functionality. They’re generally used by mobile app developers to provide analytics and data about the use of an app, or to serve advertising. You can usually limit the reporting from the app settings, or by limiting or resetting the Ad ID in your device settings.
